Guide to the Clark, Hall, and Peck and White Brothers Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Clark, Hall and Peck, 1890s-1982; Series II
  - Other Connecticut cities and towns
    - Flat files (Numerical)
      - 1482, 1484, 1485, 1691, 1784 (Box 1663)
      - 1972, 2058, 2105, 2133, 2429, 2444, 2448 (Box 1664)
      - 2526, 2535, 2584, 2658, 2663, 2731, 2827, 2861 (Box 1665)
      - 2887, 2915, 2959 (Box 1666)
      - 3236, 3273, 3314, 3331 (Box 1667)
      - 3370, 3475, 3600, 3614, 3666, 3723, 3770 (Box 1668)
      - 3821, 3849, 3910, 3995, 3997, 4002 (Box 1669)
      - 4104, 4170, 4228 (Box 1670)
      - 4248, 4271, 4411, 4472, 4493, 4498 (Box 1671)
      - 4559, 4574, 4719, 4730, 4736, 4755 (Box 1672)
      - 4926, 5126, 5171, 5197 (Box 1673)
      - 5258, 5292, 5299, 5325, 5360, 5422 (Box 1674)
      - 5442, 5512, 5516, 5527, 5548, 5618, 5634 (Box 1675)
      - 5825, 5835, 5849, 6345, 6429, 6436, 6451, 6491 (Box 1676)
      - 6549, 6577, 6611, 6710, 6764, 6812, 6832 (Box 1677)
      - 6843, 6883, 6911, 6942, 6966, 7117 (Box 1678)
      - 7152, 7262, 7264, 7267, 7290, 7310, 7378, 7411 (Box 1679)
      - 7610, 7640, 7727, 7738 (Box 1680)
      - 7783, 7896, 7951 (Box 1681)
      - 8249, 8259, 8342, 8348, 8420, 8453 (Box 1682)
      - 8461, 8556 (Box 1683)
      - 8582, 8692, 9226-9227, 9367 (Box 1684)
      - 9368 (Box 1685)
      - 9488, 9538, 9683, 9691, 9782 (Box 1686)
      - 10007, 10016, 10220, 10223, 10273, 10413, 10417 (Box 1687)
      - 10451 (Box 1688)
      - Flat files- South Central Connecticut Regional Water Authority (Box 1689)
    - Hartford abstract of title (Box 1690)
    - Huntington abstract of title (Box 1690)
    - Killingworth
      See also: New Haven County Atlas, Box 1323, for locations
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-55 (Box 1690)
        - 56-123 (Box 1691)
        - 124-155 (Box 1692)
      - Flat files
        - 6, 10-11, 18, 21, 30, 36 (Box 1693)
        - 67, 119, 149, 153 (Box 1694)
    - Litchfield abstracts of title (Box 1695)
    - Lyme abstracts of title (Box 1695)
    - Madison
      - Index card locator files
        - Streets (A-Z) (Box 1696)
        - Names of owners (A-Z) (Box 1697)
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-56 (Box 1698)
        - 57-129 (Box 1699)
        - 130-190 (Box 1700)
        - 191-259 (Box 1701)
        - 260-335 (Box 1702)
        - 336-405 (Box 1703)
        - 406-456 (Box 1704)
        - 457-531 (Box 1705)
        - 532-608 (Box 1706)
        - 609-696 (Box 1707)
        - 697-781 (Box 1708)
        - 782-860 (Box 1709)
      - Flat files
        - 96, 154, 163, 181, 182, 188, 211, 225, 235, 245, 262 (Box 1710)
        - 273, 315, 347, 369, 490, 562, 656, 668, 675 (Box 1711)
        - 703, 725, 732-733, 740, 746, 768, 789, 806, 846 (Box 1712)
    - Manchester abstracts of title (Box 1713)
    - Meriden
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-51 (Box 1713)
        - 52-87 (Box 1714)
      - Flat files (Box 1715)
    - Middlebury abstracts of title (Box 1716)
    - Middletown
      - Abstracts of title (Box 1716)
      - Flat files (Box 1716)
    - Milford
      - Atlas (Key for locations) (Box 1717)
      - Map (Key for locations) (Box 1717A)
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-70 (Box 1718)
        - 71-140 (Box 1719)
        - 141-210 (Box 1720)
        - 211-290 (Box 1721)
        - 291-358 (Box 1722)
        - 359-425 (Box 1723)
        - 426-510 (Box 1724)
        - 511-595 (Box 1725)
        - 596-690 (Box 1726)
        - 691-765 (Box 1727)
        - 766-850 (Box 1728)
        - 851-935 (Box 1729)
        - 936-1020 (Box 1730)
        - 1021-1100 (Box 1731)
        - 1101-1185 (Box 1732)
        - 1186-1275 (Box 1733)
        - 1276-1370 (Box 1734)
        - 1371-1440 (Box 1735)
        - 1441-1525 (Box 1736)
        - 1526-1610 (Box 1737)
        - 1611-1690 (Box 1738)
        - 1691-1780 (Box 1739)
        - 1781-1865 (Box 1740)
        - 1866-1951 (Box 1741)
        - 1952-2065 (Box 1742)
        - 2066-2190 (Box 1743)
        - 2191-2325 (Box 1744)
        - 2326-2470 (Box 1745)
        - 2471-2580 (Box 1746)
        - 2581-2700 (Box 1747)
        - 2701-2800 (Box 1748)
        - 2801-2930 (Box 1749)
        - 2931-3060 (Box 1750)
        - 3061-3190 (Box 1751)
        - 3191-3305 (Box 1752)
        - 3306-3435 (Box 1753)
        - 3436-3550 (Box 1754)
        - 3551-3670 (Box 1755)
        - 3671-3800 (Box 1756)
        - 3801-3905 (Box 1757)
        - 3906-4045 (Box 1758)
        - 4046-4171 (Box 1759)
        - 4172-4310 (Box 1760)
        - 4311-4450 (Box 1761)
        - 4451-4567 (Box 1762)
        - 4568-4710 (Box 1763)
        - 4711-4823 (Box 1764)
        - 4824-4960 (Box 1765)
        - 4961-5074 (Box 1766)
        - 5075-5174 (Box 1767)
        - 5175-5285 (Box 1768)
        - 5286-5415 (Box 1769)
        - 5416-5560 (Box 1770)
        - 5561-5665 (Box 1771)
        - 5666-5800 (Box 1772)
        - 5801-5936 (Box 1773)
        - 5937-6035 (Box 1774)
        - 6036-6150 (Box 1775)
        - 6151-6250 (Box 1776)
        - 6251-6355 (Box 1777)
        - 6356-6443 (Box 1778)
        - 6444-6515 (Box 1779)
        - 6516-6668 (Box 1780)
      - Flat files (Numerical)
        - 6, 10, 12, 48, 95, 105 (Box 1781)
        - 121, 127, 145, 205, 226, 247 (Box 1782)
        - 268, 282, 285, 312, 313, 346, 378, 379 (Box 1783)
        - 383, 425, 430, 439, 515, 549, 555 (Box 1784)
        - 558, 569, 570, 594, 611, 636, 641, 656, 678, 695-696, 739, 804, 852 (Box 1785)
        - 946, 964, 1001, 1011, 1023, 1029, 1038, 1112, 1174, 1180, 1223, 1229, 1243, 1255 (Box 1786)
        - 1268, 1354, 1474, 1532, 1717, 1854 (Box 1787)
        - 1887, 1903, 1980, 2024, 2043, 2044, 2045, 2046, 2047, 2048, 2049, 2050, 2281, 2287 (Box 1788)
        - 2291, 2538, 2584, 2726, 2773, 2803, 2829, 2838, 3140, 3378, 3380, 3486 (Box 1789)
        - 3525, 3557, 3753, 3809, 3816 (Box 1790)
        - 4247, 4251, 4311, 4415, 4425, 4440, 4505 (Box 1791)
        - 4612, 4655, 4737, 4766, 4874, 4914, 4961 (Box 1792)
        - 5064-5068, 5073-5074, 5077, 5093, 5180 (Box 1793)
        - 5250, 5281, 5288, 5486, 5675, 5690, 5707, 5778 (Box 1794)
        - 5899, 5998, 5999, 6011, 6070, 6084, 6086, 6123, 6199, 6243, 6262 (Box 1795)
        - 6285, 6293, 6314, 6324, 6339, 6354, 6448, 6460, 6476, 6556 (Box 1796)
      - Flat files (Alphabetical), Milford Nike site (Box 1796)
    - Monroe abstract of title (Box 1797)
    - Montville
      - Abstracts of title (Box 1797)
      - Flat file (Box 1797)
    - Naugatuck
      - Abstracts of title, 1-91 (Box 1798)
      - Flat files (Box 1799)
    - New Britain
      - Abstracts of title (Box 1800)
      - Flat file (Box 1800)
    - New Canaan abstract of title (Box 1800)
    - New London abstracts of title (Box 1800)
    - New Milford abstracts of title (Box 1800)
    - Newington abstract of title (Box 1800)
    - Newton abstracts of title (Box 1800)
    - Norfolk abstract of title (Box 1800)
    - North Branford
      - Atlas (Key for locations) (Box 1801)
      - Index card locator files
        - Streets
          - A-M (Box 1802)
          - N-Z (Box 1803)
        - Names of owners
          - A-Z (Box 1804)
        - Abstracts of title
          - 1-50 (Box 1805)
          - 51-100 (Box 1806)
          - 101-160 (Box 1807)
          - 161-230 (Box 1808)
          - 231-280 (Box 1809)
          - 281-350 (Box 1810)
          - 351-460 (Box 1811)
          - 461-545 (Box 1812)
          - 546-670 (Box 1813)
          - 671-770 (Box 1814)
          - 771-859 (Box 1815)
          - 860-984 (Box 1816)
          - 985-1076 (Box 1817)
          - 1077-1169 (Box 1818)
        - Flat files
          - 29, 32, 45, 73, 92, 117 (Box 1819)
          - 122, 128, 147, 163, 177 (Box 1820)
          - 181, 227-228, 248, 255, 292, 297, 321, 360 (Box 1821)
          - 365, 369-371, 389, 466 (Box 1822)
          - 487, 530, 542, 574, 613, 631, 641, 655 (Box 1823)
          - 667, 683, 786, 813, 859 (Box 1824)
          - 910, 925, 941, 1004, 1136, 1146-1147 (Box 1825)
          - Unnumbered file (Box 1826)
    - North Haven
      - Atlas (Key for locations) (Box 1827)
      - Index card locator files
        - Streets
          - Airline Railroad-Ferro Lane (Box 1828)
          - Fitch Street - Locke Road (Box 1829)
          - Locust Street - Poole Road (Box 1830)
          - Poplar Street - South Street (Box 1831)
          - Spring Street - Woodside Drive (Box 1832)
        - Names of owners
          - Aase - Dexter (Box 1833)
          - Dickerson - Judge (Box 1834)
          - Kaczynski - Pyrdol (Box 1835)
          - Quarz -Zygalinski (Box 1836)
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-55 (Box 1837)
        - 56-113 (Box 1838)
        - 114-172 (Box 1839)
        - 173-213 (Box 1840)
        - 214-250 (Box 1841)
        - 251-300 (Box 1842)
        - 301-353 (Box 1843)
        - 354-407 (Box 1844)
        - 408-458 (Box 1845)
        - 459-510 (Box 1846)
        - 511-570 (Box 1847)
        - 571-625 (Box 1848)
        - 626-695 (Box 1849)
        - 696-757 (Box 1850)
        - 758-839 (Box 1851)
        - 840-929 (Box 1852)
        - 930-995 (Box 1853)
        - 996-1060 (Box 1854)
        - 1061-1140 (Box 1855)
        - 1141-1202 (Box 1856)
        - 1203-1300 (Box 1857)
        - 1301-1415 (Box 1858)
        - 1416-1505 (Box 1859)
        - 1506-1610 (Box 1860)
        - 1611-1725 (Box 1861)
        - 1726-1829 (Box 1862)
        - 1830-1935 (Box 1863)
        - 1936-2025 (Box 1864)
        - 2026-2120 (Box 1865)
        - 2121-2220 (Box 1866)
        - 2221-2305 (Box 1867)
        - 2306-2405 (Box 1868)
        - 2406-2500 (Box 1869)
        - 2501-2600 (Box 1870)
        - 2601-2720 (Box 1871)
        - 2721-2830 (Box 1872)
        - 2831-2950 (Box 1873)
        - 2951-3065 (Box 1874)
        - 3066-3163 (Box 1875)
        - 3164-3270 (Box 1876)
        - 3271-3405 (Box 1877)
        - 3406-3505 (Box 1878)
        - 3506-3629 (Box 1879)
        - 3630-3716 (Box 1880)
        - 3717-3842 (Box 1881)
        - 3843-3940 (Box 1882)
        - 3941-4060 (Box 1883)
        - 4061-4160 (Box 1884)
        - 4161-4268 (Box 1885)
      - Flat files
        - 50, 75, 76, 80, 101, 108 (Box 1886)
        - 126, 129, 141, 154, 164, 168, 174 (Box 1887)
        - 187, 199, 273, 321, 399, 456 (Box 1888)
        - 462, 526, 535, 585, 598 (Box 1889)
        - 622, 768, 777, 858, 897, 902, 933, 944 (Box 1890)
        - 998, 1021, 1037, 1039, 1265, 1266, 1364 (Box 1891)
        - 1019 & 2471 and Wallingford 367 (Box 1891A)
        - 1384, 1403, 1412, 1416, 1432, 1491-1492 (Box 1892)
        - 1543, 1546, 1676, 1719, 1733, 1799, 1834 (Box 1893)
        - 1858, 1918, 2003, 2041, 2139, 2196, 2368, 2392 (Box 1894)
        - 2397, 2432, 2487, 2655 (Box 1895)
        - 2665, 2727, 3020, 3169, 3208, 3344, 3351 (Box 1896)
        - 3374, 3377, 3391, 3456, 3495, 3550, 3596, 3759, 3837, 3850 (Box 1897)
        - 4094, 4140, 4198, 4230, 4243 (Box 1898)
    - Norfolk abstracts of title (Box 1899)
    - Norwich abstracts of title (Box 1899)
    - Old Lyme
      - Abstracts of title (Box 1899)
      - Flat files (Box 1900)
    - Old Saybrook
      - Abstracts of title, 1-41 (Box 1901)
      - Flat files (Box 1901A)
    - Orange
      See also: West Haven abstracts of title and flat files 14-1 through 14-2085 in Boxes 2041-2085 and 2090-2095
      - Atlas (Key for locations) (Box 1902)
      - Index card locator files
        - Streets
          - A-N (Box 1903)
          - O-Z (Box 1904)
        - Names of owners
          - A-C (Box 1904)
          - D-Z (Box 1905)
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-105 (Box 1906)
        - 106-215 (Box 1907)
        - 216-335 (Box 1908)
        - 336-450 (Box 1909)
        - 451-555 (Box 1910)
        - 556-680 (Box 1911)
        - 681-820 (Box 1912)
        - 821-950 (Box 1913)
        - 951-1040 (Box 1914)
        - 1041-1150 (Box 1915)
        - 1151-1235 (Box 1916)
        - 1236-1344 (Box 1917)
      - Flat files
        - 24, 221, 305, 340, 519, 618, 650 (Box 1918)
        - 651, 667, 761, 787, 813, 826, 928, 1064 (Box 1919)
        - 1066, 1079, 1149, 1321 (Box 1920)
    - Oxford
      - Abstracts of title, 1-45 (Box 1921)
      - Flat files
        - 3-4, 28-30, 34 (Box 1922)
        - 39-41 (Box 1923)
    - Plainville flat file (Box 1924)
    - Plymouth abstracts of title (Box 1924)
    - Prospect
      See also: Bethany, Prospect and Woodbridge Atlas, Box 1329, for locations
      - Abstracts of title (Box 1925)
      - Flat file (Box 1925)
    - Putnam abstract of title (Box 1926)
    - Ridgefield abstracts of title (Box 1926)
    - Salem
      - Abstracts of title (Box 1926)
      - Flat files (Box 1926)
    - Salisbury abstracts of title (Box 1927)
    - Saybrook abstract of title (Box 1927)
    - Seymour
      - Abstracts of title, 1-85 (Box 1927)
      - Flat files
        - 24, 27, 37, 44, 63, 64, 65 (Box 1928)
        - 66-67, 71, 76, 86 (Box 1929)
      - Index card locator file (Streets and owner names) (Box 1929A)
    - Sharon abstracts of title (Box 1930)
    - Shelton
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-43 (Box 1930)
        - 44-63 (Box 1931)
      - Flat files, 49, 54, 59 (Box 1931)
    - Southbury
      - Abstracts of title (Box 1932)
      - Flat file (Box 1932)
    - Southington abstracts of title (Box 1932)
    - Stamford abstracts of title (Box 1932)
    - Sterling abstract of title (Box 1932)
    - Stratford
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-90 (Box 1933)
        - 91-147 (Box 1934)
      - Flat files
        - 20 (Box 1935)
        - 132, 136-139 (Box 1936)
    - Thompson
      - Abstracts of title (Box 1937)
      - Flat file (Box 1937)
    - Trumbull abstracts of title (Box 1937)
    - Wallingford
      - Index card locator files
        - Streets
          - A-M (Box 1938)
          - N-Z (Box 1939)
        - Names of owners, A-Z (Box 1940)
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-65 (Box 1941)
        - 66-135 (Box 1942)
        - 136-240 (Box 1943)
        - 241-335 (Box 1944)
        - 336-450 (Box 1945)
        - 451-535 (Box 1946)
        - 536-620 (Box 1947)
        - 621-715 (Box 1948)
        - 716-790 (Box 1949)
        - 791-900 (Box 1950)
        - 901-999 (Box 1951)
        - 1000-1065 (Box 1952)
      - Flat files
        - 60-65, 77, 82, 85 (Box 1953)
        - 88, 90, 98, 105, 113, 118, 121 (Box 1954)
        - 127, 146, 185-188, 201, 206 (Box 1955)
        - 208, 228, 239, 253, 285, 307, 309, 330, 338, 345, 357 (Box 1956)
        - 387, 412, 436, 445, 448, 515, 541, 624, 631, 637, 667, 676 (Box 1957)
        - 684, 729, 732, 736, 759-764, 799 (Box 1958)
        - 800-802, 805, 806, 808, 835, 837, 860, 894, 902, 910, 915, 920, 926, 930, 932 (Box 1959)
        - 958, 962, 983, 992, 1003, 1010 (Box 1960)
        - 1034, 1040 (Box 1961)
    - Waterbury
      - Abstracts of title, 1-66 (Box 1962)
      - Flat file, 55, 62 (Box 1963)
    - West Hartford abstracts of title
    - West Haven
      - Index card locator files
        - Streets
          - Abner Street - Bellevue Avenue (Box 1964)
          - Benham Hill Road - Center Street (Box 1965)
          - Central Avenue - Dawson Avenue (Box 1966)
          - Dayton Street - First Avenue (Box 1967)
          - Flaum Drive - Highland Street (Box 1968)
          - Highview Street - Kelsey Avenue (Box 1969)
          - Kelsey Court - Marion Street (Box 1970)
          - Marks Drive - Ocala Street (Box 1971)
          - Ocean Avenue - Pent Road (Box 1972)
          - Phillips Terrace - Savin Rock (Box 1973)
          - Saw Mill Road - Thall Street (Box 1974)
          - Third Avenue - Washington Manor Avenue (Box 1975)
          - Water Street - Zegmont Street (Box 1976)
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-1 -1-85 (Box 1977)
        - 1-86 -1-200 (Box 1978)
        - 1-201 -1-324 (Box 1979)
        - 2-1 -2-85 (Box 1980)
        - 2-86 -2-170 (Box 1981)
        - 2-171 -2-265 (Box 1982)
        - 3-1 -3-65 (Box 1983)
        - 3-66 -3-140 (Box 1984)
        - 3-141 -3-210 (Box 1985)
        - 3-211 -3-305 (Box 1986)
        - 3-306 -3-400 (Box 1987)
        - 3-401 -3-500 (Box 1988)
        - 3-501 -3-610 (Box 1989)
        - 3-611 -3-729 (Box 1990)
        - 4-1 -4-80 (Box 1991)
        - 4-81 -4-165 (Box 1992)
        - 4-166 -4-260 (Box 1993)
        - 4-261 -4-350 (Box 1994)
        - 4-351 -4-450 (Box 1995)
        - 4-451 -4-564 (Box 1996)
        - 5-1 -5-75 (Box 1997)
        - 5-76 -5-113, 6-1 -6-25 (Box 1998)
        - 6-26 -6-111 (Box 1999)
        - 7-1 -7-55 (Box 2000)
        - 7-56 -7-125 (Box 2001)
        - 7-126 -7-209 (Box 2002)
        - 8-1 -8-60 (Box 2003)
        - 8-61 -8-140 (Box 2004)
        - 8-141 -8-215 (Box 2005)
        - 8-216 -8-310 (Box 2006)
        - 8-311 -8-431 (Box 2007)
        - 9-1 -9-60 (Box 2008)
        - 9-61 -9-146 (Box 2009)
        - 10-1 -10-85 (Box 2010)
        - 10-86 -10-175 (Box 2011)
        - 10-176 -10-280 (Box 2012)
        - 10-281 -10-426 (Box 2013)
        - 11-1 -11-85 (Box 2014)
        - 11-86 -11-155 (Box 2015)
        - 11-156 -11-250 (Box 2016)
        - 11-251 -11- 363 (Box 2017)
        - 11-364 -11-470 (Box 2018)
        - 11-471 -11-570 (Box 2019)
        - 11-571 -11-665 (Box 2020)
        - 11-666 -11-740 (Box 2021)
        - 11-741 -11-831 (Box 2022)
        - 12-1 -12-80 (Box 2023)
        - 12-81 -12-170 (Box 2024)
        - 12-171 -12-250 (Box 2025)
        - 12-251 -12-360 (Box 2026)
        - 13-1 -13-50 (Box 2027)
        - 13-51 -13-130 (Box 2028)
        - 13-131 -13-225 (Box 2029)
        - 13-226 -13-300 (Box 2030)
        - 13-301 -13-390 (Box 2031)
        - 13-391 -13-500 (Box 2032)
        - 13-501 -13-600 (Box 2033)
        - 13-601 -13-700 (Box 2034)
        - 13-701 -13-800 (Box 2035)
        - 13-801 -13-935 (Box 2036)
        - 13-936 -13-1050 (Box 2037)
        - 13-1051 -13-1195 (Box 2038)
        - 13-1196 -13-1320 (Box 2039)
        - 13-1321 -13-1456 (Box 2040)
        - 14-1 -14-55 (Box 2041)
        - 14-56 -14-110 (Box 2042)
        - 14-111 -14-175 (Box 2043)
        - 14-176 -14-225 (Box 2044)
        - 14-226 -14-295 (Box 2045)
        - 14-296 -14-370 (Box 2046)
        - 14-371 -14-440 (Box 2047)
        - 14-441 -14-515 (Box 2048)
        - 14-516 -14-575 (Box 2049)
        - 14-576 -14-671 (Box 2050)
        - 14-672 -14-750 (Box 2051)
        - 14-751 -14-840 (Box 2052)
        - 14-841 -14-950 (Box 2053)
        - 14-951 -14-1034 (Box 2054)
        - 14-1035 -14-1115 (Box 2055)
        - 14-1116 -14-1215 (Box 2056)
        - 14-1216 -14-1284 (Box 2057)
        - 14-1285 -14-1370 (Box 2058)
        - 14-1371 -14-1455 (Box 2059)
        - 14-1456 -14-1560 (Box 2060)
        - 14-1561 -14-1660 (Box 2061)
        - 14-1661 -14-1769 (Box 2062)
        - 14-1770 -14-1875 (Box 2063)
        - 14-1876 -14-1984 (Box 2064)
        - 14-1985 -14-2085 (Box 2065)
        - West Haven 1- West Haven 105 (Box 2066)
        - West Haven 106- West Haven 235 (Box 2067)
        - West Haven 236- West Haven 350 (Box 2068)
        - West Haven 351- West Haven 500 (Box 2069)
        - West Haven 501- West Haven 630 (Box 2070)
        - West Haven 631-West Haven 800 (Box 2071)
        - West Haven 801-West Haven 935 (Box 2072)
        - West Haven 936-West Haven 1070 (Box 2073)
        - West Haven 1071-West Haven 1170 (Box 2074)
        - West Haven 1171- West Haven 1270 (Box 2075)
        - West Haven 1271- West Haven 1390 (Box 2076)
        - West Haven 1391-West Haven 1489 (Box 2077)
      - Flat files
        - 7-40, 7-114, 7-131, 8-234, 8-430 (Box 2078)
        - 9-12, 9-68, 9-135, 10-37, 10-128, 11-39 (Box 2079)
        - 11-299, 11-651, 13-14, 13-163 (Box 2080)
        - 13-127, 13-501 (Box 2081)
        - 13-509, 13-820, 13-876, 13-1015-1018, 13-1041, 13-1336, 13-1438, 14-49, 14-86 (Box 2082)
        - 14-101, 14-119 (Box 2083)
        - 14-225 (Box 2084)
        - 14-225 Supplement, 14-357, 14-359 (Box 2085)
        - 14-682, 14-707, 14-891, 14-894, 14-954, 14-1619, 14-1782 (Box 2086)
        - West Haven 357, West Haven 553, West Haven 891, West Haven 950, West Haven 966, West Haven 1000 (Box 2087)
        - West Haven 1044, West Haven 1145, West Haven 1147, West Haven 1163-1164, West Haven 1349 (Box 2088)
        - West Haven 1392, West Haven 1463 (Box 2089)
      - Flat files (Orange flat files in West Haven District 14)
        - 14-22, 14-91, 14-29, 14-91, 14-265, 14-268, 14-270, 14-271, 14-314 (Box 2090)
        - 14-333, 14-350, 14-421 (Box 2091)
        - 14-779, 14-785, 14-917, 14-935, 14-966, 14-1149, 14-1180 (Box 2092)
        - 14-553, 14-1647, 14-1655, 14-1700 (Box 2093)
        - (14-834, 14-1701), 14-1724 (Box 2094)
        - 14-1727, 14-1800, 14-1973 (Box 2095)
      - Flat files (Orange alphabetical in West Haven District 14), U.S. Nike site (Box 2096)
    - Westbrook
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-40 (Box 2096)
        - 41-73 (Box 2097)
      - Flat files, 37, 51, 53 (Box 2098)
    - Westport abstracts of title (Box 2099)
    - Wilton abstracts of title (Box 2099)
    - Wolcott abstracts of title (Box 2099)
    - Woodbridge
      - Index card locator files
        - Streets
          - A-L (Box 2100)
          - M-Z (Box 2101)
        - Names of owners
          - A-L (Box 2102)
          - M-Z (Box 2103)
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-50 (Box 2104)
        - 51-95 (Box 2105)
        - 96-140 (Box 2106)
        - 141-180 (Box 2107)
        - 181-216 (Box 2108)
        - 217-255 (Box 2109)
        - 256-295 (Box 2110)
        - 296-336 (Box 2111)
        - 337-380 (Box 2112)
        - 381-455 (Box 2113)
        - 456-502 (Box 2114)
        - 503-570 (Box 2115)
        - 571-655 (Box 2116)
        - 656-740 (Box 2117)
        - 741-840 (Box 2118)
        - 841-960 (Box 2119)
        - 961-1050 (Box 2120)
        - 1051-1180 (Box 2121)
        - 1181-1270 (Box 2122)
        - 1271-1370 (Box 2123)
        - 1371-1480 (Box 2124)
        - 1481-1565 (Box 2125)
        - 1566-1640 (Box 2126)
        - 1641-1681 (Box 2127)
      - Flat files
        - 15, 21, 57, 112 (Box 2128)
        - 116, 157, 178, 210, 228, 263 (Box 2129)
        - 296, 307, 327, 397 (Box 2130)
        - 426, 427, 445, 455, 526, 616, 651, 678, 714 (Box 2131)
        - 724, 744, 752, 766, 870, 917, 949, 1000, 1151, 1168, 1197, 1395 (Box 2132)
    - Woodbury abstracts of title (Box 2133)
  - Index card file of the names of owners for all Clark, Hall & Peck title searches in all towns and cities
    - A & A Enterprises Inc. - Alleman (Box 2134)
    - Allen - Angello (Box 2135)
    - Angelo - Avoletta (Box 2136)
    - Avon Realty Co. - Baroncini (Box 2137)
    - Barone - Behning (Box 2138)
    - Behnke - Bethany Enterprises Inc. (Box 2139)
    - Bethea - Bolek (Box 2140)
    - Boling - Brandolino (Box 2141)
    - Brandon Company - Browne (Box 2142)
    - Brownell - Buttrick (Box 2143)
    - Butts - Caracciolo (Box 2144)
    - Carafa - Cassidy (Box 2145)
    - Cassin - Chichester (Box 2146)
    - Chicoskey - Chossen (Box 2147)
    - Coad - Conners (Box 2148)
    - Connerton - Couch (Box 2149)
    - Couchon - Culotta (Box 2150)
    - Culver - Davia (Box 2151)
    - David - Delle (Box 2152)
    - Dellert - Dey (Box 2153)
    - Deyo - Don (Box 2154)
    - Donadio - duPont (Box 2155)
    - Dupre - Engels (Box 2156)
    - Engengro - Farquhrson (Box 2157)
    - Farr - Fiola (Box 2158)
    - Fiondella - Fosdick (Box 2159)
    - Foskett - Fusco (Box 2160)
    - Fussell - Geleneau (Box 2161)
    - Gelfrin - Gladding (Box 2162)
    - Gladish - Gralton (Box 2163)
    - Gramatico - Guest (Box 2164)
    - Guetens - Hansell (Box 2165)
    - Hansen - Hefka (Box 2166)
    - Heft - Hissick (Box 2167)
    - Hitchcock - Howells (Box 2168)
    - Howes - Irwin (Box 2169)
    - Isaacs - Johnson, Iver (Box 2170)
    - Johnson, J. Albert - Kasprzycki (Box 2171)
    - Kass - Kilkelly (Box 2172)
    - Killam - Kosteck (Box 2173)
    - Koster - Lamonica (Box 2174)
    - Lamont - Leapley (Box 2175)
    - Lebiger - Lebon (Box 2176)